xtremepush.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy | Xtremepush | Multi-Channel Analytics & Engagement

**Information Collection**  
In common with other websites, log files are stored on our web server saving details such as the visitor’s IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit. Where registration is required, the visitor’s email address and username will be stored on our server.

**Collection of Personal Data**  
Xtremepush collects personal data from a variety of sources including www.xtremepush.com website, exhibitions, seminars, emails and telephone call. All data is collected with the users’ permission.

Information that is collected includes names, contact details, preferences and commercial information.

**Use of Data**  
Xtremepush will use the information we collect to enhance your use of the website or to inform you of news, services, products, and promotions by us.

**Sharing of Data**  
Email addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to third parties.

**Data Management**  
If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in every email that you receive from Xtremepush.

You can also contact us directly with any questions – [Contact Us](https://xtremepush.com/contact-us/)

**Viewing Personal Data**  
At any time you may request to view the personal data that we have stored. You may also ask for your data to be removed or to opt-out of any of our communications

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser. They remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website and they may also be used to track your return visits to the site.

Third-party advertising companies may also use cookies for tracking purposes. You may block cookies via your browser setting, but doing so may prevent access to certain features of this website.

Please view our Cookies Policy [here.](https://xtremepush.com/cookies-policy-legal-statement/)

**Disclaimer**  
The content on this website is provided as an information guide only. While every effort is made to ensure the information on this site is accurate and current, XtremePush takes no responsibility for errors, omissions, or misleading statements on these pages or on any site linked to these pages.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Terms and conditions of use and all issues regarding this website shall be governed by the laws of Ireland, and The General Data Protection Regulation.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
This privacy policy may change. All updates will be posted on this page.
